Guide to the Shepherd Stevens Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Papers of Stevens's family members, 1822-1931; Series XIII
  - William Stokes Boyd (great-uncle)
    - Financial records and coat of arms, 1897, undated (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - Photographs
      - 1822, 1887 (Box 101, Folder 29)
      - Daguerreotypes, Undated (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Photograph album--portraits, 1873 (Box 103)
  - Geo F. Shepherd (great-uncle)
    - Correspondence and financial records, 1853-1857 (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - Photographs
      - Daguerreotypes, Undated (Box 100, Folder 2-4)
        Includes Geo F. Shepherd in his Washington Grays
      - Daguerreotype of James Shepherd (brother), Undated (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Undated (Box 95, Folder 15-16)